[Music]
your benefits your way with the Manulife
mobile app let's take a look at how to
check your claim coverage and
balances log in the manual lifee mobile
app and select
coverage choose the type of balance and
service you're searching for from there
you can see what remaining balance or
occurrences you have left for the
specific
service you you can also review all your
recent claims and past statements on the
manual lifee mobile app here's how
return to the main navigation and click
on claims then select the claim you wish
to review managing your claims has never
been easier and faster with the manual
lifee mobile app